{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of superheroes!",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Bruce Wayne?",
      "answers": ["Batman", "Ironman", "Superman"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Thor's weapon?",
      "answers": ["Mjolnir", "Sword", "Shield"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Peter Parker?",
      "answers": ["Hulk", "Flash", "Spiderman"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Superman's weakness?",
      "answers": ["Fire", "Iron", "Kryptonite"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the Black Panther?",
      "answers": ["T'Challa", "Tony", "Clark"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Wonder Woman?",
      "answers": ["Diana", "Natasha", "Lois"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Tony Stark's suit called?",
      "answers": ["Bat", "Iron", "Spider"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the God of Mischief?",
      "answers": ["Loki", "Thor", "Hades"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What color is Hulk?",
      "answers": ["Blue", "Red", "Green"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Steve Rogers?",
      "answers": ["Batman", "Ironman", "Cap"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Wolverine's claws made of?",
      "answers": ["Steel", "Vibranium", "Adamantium"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who leads the X-Men?",
      "answers": ["Logan", "Magneto", "Charles"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Green Lantern's power source?",
      "answers": ["Ring", "Crown", "Cape"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Superman from?",
      "answers": ["Krypton", "Mars", "Earth"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who can shrink in size?",
      "answers": ["Flash", "Ant-Man", "Thor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Flash's power?",
      "answers": ["Strength", "Speed", "Flight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Black Widow use?",
      "answers": ["Guns", "Magic", "Lasers"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Aquaman?",
      "answers": ["Arthur", "Clark", "Steve"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Hawkeye use?",
      "answers": ["Sword", "Gun", "Bow"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Captain Marvel's name?",
      "answers": ["Carol", "Diana", "Natasha"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
